I just wanted to remind everyone who has been raising their voices and using
their platform to speak about Palestine, who you are fighting against and who you
are kicking the ass of. Did you know that in 2015 Benyamin Netanyahu founded the
Ministry of Strategic Affairs just for the sole purposes of fighting boycotts
and divestment attempts and that from 2016 to 2019 he has invested one hundred
million dollars into hiring the best people in the field to spread this
information about the plight of the Palestinians? And why is that important
you say? Because we're not just proving them wrong and we're not just proving a
whole system of American propaganda wrong. We are proving capitalism wrong. What we
are doing shouldn't be possible. We are a loose coalition of people of goodwill that
are not being paid for doing what we're doing. There is no monetary incentive.
There is a community incentive to safeguard people who are the subject of
oppression. There's no central coordination. Just us. From political
scientists to experts in posting funny pictures on the internet. From people who
are able to send emails to people who are able to go out in the streets. From
storytellers to mathematicians to human rights experts. We are forcing people to
do what the Palestinians have asked us continuously to do. We're forcing them to
look. So take heart. Because whatever minimal thing that you are doing is working.